<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Item name in the drawer and toolbar -->
    <string name="section_eight">Theme Info</string>

    <!-- Tab titles -->
    <string-array name="info_sections">
        <item>FAQ</item>
        <item>Themed Apps</item>
        <item>Bugs/Issues</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Tab contents -->
    <string-array name="info_contents">
        <item>Welcome to the info section! Please take a moment to carefully read the section below if you have any bugs or concerns
            \n\nREBOOT YOUR PHONE BEFORE SENDING BUG REPORTS.
            \n\nI\'ve received way too many bug reports that were solved with a simple restart. Additionally, DO NOT SUBMIT REPORTS IF YOU HAVE XPOSED INSTALLED. The least you could do is disable all the modules and try again. However, if you have any other bug reports, please note that screenshots help a lot with the fixes.
            \n\nAnother common issue results from not having an updated rom; you MUST have a rom with the latest updated commits for this theme to properly function. New tweaks are added every day, and as of now the major changes were merged in early March. As such, if you don\'t have those commits, you will see issues that I won\'t be able to fix. Pay special attention to AOSP apps. If they are built into most roms, you can expect me to notice it if something is horribly wrong.
            \n\nMake sure you have a rom with the latest cm theme commits for everything to work properly. New changes are constantly added, so please check and use the latest rom before filing reports. Pay special attention to AOSP apps. If they are built into most roms, you can expect me to notice it if something is horribly wrong.
            \n\nHowever, please also note that newer roms like Cyanogen OS (not the same as CyanogenMod) do not have the commits either, so there will be some incompatibilities with it; but since you have the app themer there it shouldn\'t be a problem.
            \n\nThis theme should technically never put you into a bootloop, but odd things do happen occasionally to some people. In the event that it occurs, first check to see what you have applied in the theme. Note that the bootanimation is tailored to xhdpi phones (originally xxhdpi, but I made that a separate zip to support more phones), so it may cause issues on low end devices. If the problem persists, you can always go into the TWRP (recovery) file manager and delete the apk from there. At the end of the day, please understand that the theme chooser is still in alpha, and whatever you do is your own responsibility. I have no intentions of messing up your phone, but you\'ll have to be prepared to deal with it if it happens. This theme is my daily and I can say at least for myself that it is extremely stable.
            \n\nIf an app has a light and a dark theme, I likely themed the dark one. In that case, the light version may even become unusable, so make sure you switch. For other apps like the keyboards, I themed the light version as transparent (for this theme essentially) and dark as pure black.
            \n\nPlease also understand that I am one themer with one phone. Apart from a Nexus 5, powered by a few selected roms, this theme hasn\'t been officially tested. It does however work for most users, which is a positive sign.
        </item>
        <item>SYSTEM
            \n\n&#8226; Framework-res
            \n&#8226; SystemUI
            \n&#8226; Settings
            \n&#8226; Cell Broadcast Receiver
            \n&#8226; Documents UI
            \n&#8226; Face Lock
            \n&#8226; Phone
            \n&#8226; Telecom
            \n&#8226; CyanogenMod Account
            \n&#8226; CyanogenMod Music Player (Eleven)
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod Lock Clock
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod Setup Wizard
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod Trebuchet
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod Updater
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod Theme Chooser
            \n&#8226; Cyanogenmod AudioFx
            \n&#8226; Euphoria OTA
            \n&#8226; Package Installer
            \n\nAOSP
            \n\n&#8226; Calculator
            \n&#8226; Contacts
            \n&#8226; Desk Clock
            \n&#8226; Dialer
            \n&#8226; AOSP Keyboard
            \n&#8226; Launcher 3
            \n&#8226; MMS
            \n\nGOOGLE
            \n\n&#8226; Google +
            \n&#8226; Gmail
            \n&#8226; Google Search
            \n&#8226; Google Now
            \n&#8226; Drive
            \n&#8226; Youtube (bug fix only)
            \n&#8226; Google Keyboard
            \n&#8226; Google Handwriting
            \n\nUSER
            \n\n&#8226; K9-Mail
            \n&#8226; Snapchat (light touches)
            \n&#8226; Nova Launcher
            \n&#8226; Hells Core Kernel Updater
            \n&#8226; Switchr
            \n&#8226; Kernel Adiutor (use dark theme)
            \n&#8226; Ebay (notification fix)
            \n&#8226; Swype (modified material dark theme)
            \n\nXPOSED
            \n\n&#8226; Xposed Framework
            \n&#8226; Notification Manager
            \n&#8226; SnapPref
            \n&#8226; SnapColors
            \n&#8226; Native Clipboard
            \n\nIN THE XDA BETA
            \n\n&#8226; Adobe Acrobat
            \n&#8226; Google Services
            \n&#8226; Google Games
            \n&#8226; ModernHub
            \n&#8226; Inbox
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Dialer and Contacts have unpredictable crashes, especially with custom DPI\'s or low DPI
            \n&#8226; Dialer and Contacts cannot be made transparent; black for now
            \n&#8226; AOSP bugs: please read the FAQ
            \n&#8226; Gmail has a white background in the two pane view. This color is hardcoded in a layouts file (two_pane_activity.xml) and can\'t be changed. Furthermore, I don\'t have a tablet and won\'t be spending a lot of energy in fixing a bug I can\'t test.
            \n&#8226; Ambient display has black text: this was fixed in mid April, so make sure you have the latest commits in your rom.
            \n&#8226; Blisspop sometimes has incompatibilities. Please note that this rom is heavily modified, and deviates quite a lot from standard AOSP. As such, it may not always work with this theme.
            \n&#8226; Some issues with Cyanogen OS; Note that they have not merged the latest theme commits, which is why it isn\'t working. It\'s up to them to update it, and us themers can\'t do anything about it yet.
            \n&#8226; Whatsapp cannot be themed as it has way too many hard coded colors. However, Team Blackout has made a nice modded apk, which you can get from their downloader, which is linked in Material Glass.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>